childhoodbiography.com 2019-04-07

# Welcome to Childhood Biography Privacy Policy Page

At ChildhoodBiography.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the type of personal information that is received and collected by us and how it is been used.  
Like many other Web sites, we make use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider    (ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and a number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
ChildhoodBiography does not use cookies.  
DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ChildhoodBiography.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ChildhoodBiography.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partner include ….Google Adsense  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ChildhoodBiography.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
It is pertinent to note that ChildhoodBiography.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ChildhoodBiography privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.  
We have also implemented the following:  
§ Demographics and Interests Reporting  
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.  
Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on.  
Please feel free to contact us at childhoodbiography@gmail.com if you have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy.
